It's Hunting Season and You're the Prey
Croc is a horror, action, tv movie film directed by Stewart Raffill.
A large man-eating crocodile terrorizes tourists
and locals near Krabi, in Thailand.
Michael Madsen plays a hunter stalking the immense reptile, while sub-plots include a rivalry between a foreigner, who
owns a crocodile-farm, and a Thai man who plays a part in framing the foreigner for the crocodile's rampage.
Croc Hawkins, played by Michael Madsen.
Jack McQuade, played by Peter Tuinstra.
Evelyn Namawong, played by Sherry Edwards.
Allison, played by Elizabeth Healey.
Theo, played by Scott Hazell.
Sunee, played by Amy Lackgren.
Croc is a 2007 American made-for-television natural horror film produced by RHI Entertainment that
premiered in Canada on the video-on-demand channel Movie Central On Demand in July 2007.
It aired in the United States on the Sci Fi Channel on November 4, 2007.
Croc is the sixth film in the Maneater film series
produced under an agreement with Sci Fi.
Filmed in Thailand, the film revolves around the efforts of the owner of a crocodile-farm, an animal welfare agent,
and a hunter trying to kill a large saltwater crocodile that has begun killing people in the area.
The tone is dark.